hi.im 2019-10-02

# Privacy Policy - Koombea - Bringing apps to life

**Koombea Privacy Policy**

_Last modified: August 2, 2018_

**Introduction**

Koombea Inc. ( **“Koombea”** ) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website [www.koombea.com](http://www.koombea.com/) (our “ **Website** “) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On this Website.
  * In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this Website.
  * Through mobile and desktop applications you download from this Website, which provides dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and this Website.
  * When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * Us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Koombea or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or
  * Any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see _Changes to Our Privacy Policy_ ). Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

**Children Under the Age of 13**

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [legal@koombea.com](mailto:legal@koombea.com).

**Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It**

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

  * By which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, email address, telephone number, and any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline (“ **personal information** “);
  * That is about you but individually does not identify you; and/or
  * About your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the Website. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies.
  * From third parties, for example, our business partners.

**_Information You Provide to Us._** The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Website, subscribing to our service, posting material, or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our Website.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “ **posted** “) on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, “ **User Contributions** “). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

**_Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies._** As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking).

Please note that our Website does not support “do not track” requests.

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not include personal information, but we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include cookies and similar technologies. A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. To learn more about our use of cookies, see our [cookie policy](https://www.koombea.com/cookie-policy/).

**Third-Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website, are served by third parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see _Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information_.

**How We Use Your Information**

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To provide you with notices about your account or subscription, including expiration and renewal notices.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide through it.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third-parties’ goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, see _Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information_.

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

**Disclosure of Your Information**

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and which are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Koombea’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Koombea about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have not opted out of these disclosures. For more information, see _Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information_.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Koombea, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Data Retention**

We will retain your personal information for as long as necessary for the purpose you provided it to us. However, we may retain and use your personal information for longer periods to the extent necessary to comply with our legal (including tax and accounting) obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information**

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * **_Tracking Technologies and Advertising._** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
  * **_Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising._** If you do not want us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for promotional purposes, you can opt-out by sending us an email stating your request to [legal@koombea.com](mailto:legal@koombea.com).
  * **_Promotional Offers from the Koombea._** If you do not wish to have your contact information used by the Koombea to promote our own or third parties’ products or services, you can opt-out by sending us an email stating your request to [legal@koombea.com](mailto:legal@koombea.com). If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions.

We do not control third-parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However, these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“ **NAI** “) on the NAI’s website.

**Accessing and Correcting Your Information**

You may send us an email at [legal@koombea.com](mailto:legal@koombea.com) to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or might have been copied or stored by other Website users.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [legal@koombea.com](mailto:legal@koombea.com).

**Your European Union Data Protection Rights**

If you are located in the European Union, you have certain additional rights with respect to your personal information under the General Data Protection Regulation (Regulation (EU) 2016/679) (the “GDPR”), including the following:

  * The right of access to your personal information.
  * The right to rectify your personal information if it is incorrect or incomplete.
  * The right to have your personal information erased (“right to be forgotten”) if certain grounds are met.
  * The right to withdraw your consent to our processing of your personal information at any time (if our processing is based on consent).
  * The right to object to our processing of your personal information (if processing is based on legitimate interests).
  * The right to object to our processing of your personal information for direct marketing purposes.
  * The right to receive your personal information from us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, and the right to transmit your personal information to another controller without hindrance from us (data portability).

If you are or have been our customer, we may send you marketing communications based on our legitimate interests, subject always to your right to opt out of such communications. We will never share your personal information with a third party for such third party’s marketing purposes unless you have specifically consented to us doing so.

You may contact us at [legal@koombea.com](mailto:legal@koombea.com) to exercise any of the above rights. We may request specific information from you to confirm your identity, and in some circumstances, we may charge a reasonable fee for access to your personal information. Furthermore, if you believe that our processing of your personal information is inconsistent with your data protection rights under the GDPR and we have not adequately addressed your concerns, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the data protection supervisory authority of your country.

For purposes of the GDPR, we are a “controller” and you are a “data subject.”

**Data Security**

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure.

The safety and security of your information also depend on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

**Contact Information**

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:

Koombea Inc.  
2250 NW 114th Ave  
Unit 1L COL5242  
Miami, FL 33192

Email: [legal@koombea.com](mailto:legal@koombea.com).
